kensington.com 2019-08-23

# Privacy Policy | Kensington

This Privacy Policy was last modified and is effective as of April 10, 2018.

ACCO Brands Corporation, its subsidiaries and affiliated entities (collectively, “ACCO Brands” or “we” or “us”) recognize that you care how your information is collected and used. We have created this Privacy Policy to inform you of how we collect, use and share this information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to be sure you understand its terms. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us here.

###   
**1\. Scope of this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy applies to websites (including mobile websites), mobile applications and other digital platforms which are owned or managed by ACCO Brands and which contain or refer to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Digital Services”). It also applies to information collected through other channels that are NOT Digital Services, such as through our customer support services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any of ACCO Brands’ websites (including mobile websites), mobile applications and other digital platforms to which it is not posted or to third-party websites and platforms, even though the Digital Services may link to such websites and platforms. You can learn more about links from the Digital Services in the “Links to Other Sites” section.

This Privacy Policy describes our practices regarding both personal information and non-personal information. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, personal information is information that can be used to identify or contact a particular individual, for example: full names, addresses, and email addresses. Non-personal information, by itself, cannot be used to identify or contact a particular individual.

### **2\. Your Consent and Agreement**

This Privacy Policy forms part of your legal agreement with ACCO Brands under the Terms of Use applicable to the Digital Services. By using the Digital Services, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Digital Services.

### **3\. Modifications to this Privacy Policy**

ACCO Brands may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. Whenever this Privacy Policy is revised, we will update the “effective date” at the beginning of the Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy each time you use the Digital Services to see if the Privacy Policy has been revised since your last visit. If we make a material change to this Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on the Digital Services. By using any of the Digital Services after the effective date of any changes, you agree to the terms of the Privacy Policy as modified.

### **4\. Collection of Information**

_Information You Provide_

We collect information that you provide to us, either by entering it into the Digital Services, providing it to a customer services representative, or otherwise. For example, when you request information, inquire about our services, subscribe to our emails, ask for promotional or support materials, place an order, open or manage an account, register ACCO Brands products, enter sweepstakes, contests, and promotions (collectively, “Promotions”), participate in surveys, or apply for a job at ACCO Brands, we will ask you to provide information to complete these transactions. The information you provide may include personal information, such as your name, email address, street address, telephone number and social media account information. Additional information you may provide includes, but isn’t limited to:

  * If you log in your account, your username and password.
  * If you make a purchase, your payment information.
  * If you enter a Promotion, your age or birth date.
  * If you participate in a survey, demographic information such as your gender, age, occupation, income, ethnicity, family size and marital status, and information regarding your preferences or product choices.
  * If you share communications or content from the Digital Services with a third party the third party’s name and/or contact information.
  * If you apply for employment, your work authorization status, academic and employment history, salary history, desired salary, and any other information you submit to us or include on your resume and/or other documents you upload to the Digital Services. You may also choose to provide optional information such as race, gender, and whether you have a disability or are a Veteran.

_Information from Third Parties_

ACCO Brands may collect information about you that we receive from other sources. For example, we may receive information about you from the U.S Postal Service National Change of Address (NCOA) service and providers of consumer data. We may combine the information we receive about you from these third parties with other information we collect from you. For example, we may use the information supplied by third parties to update and correct the information contained in our databases and to provide product recommendations and special offers that we think will interest you.

We may also collect information or gain access to information from third-party social media platforms, including, without limitation, Facebook®, Twitter® and Instagram® (“Social Media Platforms”).

For example, the Digital Services may permit you to log in to or otherwise interface with a Social Media Platform from or in connection with the Digital Services. The information you submit while logging in to any social media platform while on the Digital Services is collected by the social media platform and not by ACCO Brands, but the social media platform may provide information about you, such as your user name, friend or follower lists and other information that you have made part of your public profile on that Social Media Platform, to us. In some instances, you may be able to choose which information the Social Media Platform shares with us. In other instances, the Social Media Platform, determines what information about you is shared with us. If you are already logged in to the Social Media Platform when you visit the Digital Services, the information may be provided to us automatically by the Social Media Platform.

We may combine the information received from the Social Media Platform with other information we have about you. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of each Social Media Platform you use for more information about their privacy practices, and how to adjust your settings on that Social Media Platform to meet your preferences.

_Information We Automatically Collect Through Technologies_

We capture certain information automatically whenever you visit or use the Digital Services. This information may include your Internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, operating system, device type, application software, time and date you visit or use the Digital Services, and traffic patterns and usage data, such as the pages you access, the website that directed you to the Digital Services and the website you visit when you leave the Digital Services. This information is gathered with "cookies" and/or other online tools. See the "Cookies and Other Technologies" section below for more information on how these tools work and how we use them.

The information we collect in this manner is not personal information. However, we may combine it with other information in an attempt to identify you or that does identify you.

_Location Information_

ACCO Brands may use your IP address, cookies, online tools or technologies – alone in some cases or in conjunction with other information or technologies in other cases - to derive your general location or your mailing address. However, ACCO does not track your precise physical location at any given moment in time. At present, we do not collect precise geolocation information from your mobile device. See the "Cookies and Other Technologies" section below for more information on how these tools work and how we use them. Please be aware that if you submit a digital photograph to us, it may contain location data. If you don’t want us to have such data, you should delete it prior to submitting the photograph.

### **5\. How We Use Your Information**

The information we collect is used for the purpose for which it was collected, such as to provide the information, product or service you requested or to complete a transaction. In addition, we may also use your information to or for:

  * Process, track and ship orders and manage billing and payment processes.
  * Communicate with you regarding your orders, purchases, accounts, employment applications and Promotions entries.
  * Provide customer service.
  * Prevent and investigate malicious activity, security breaches, and fraud.
  * Provide additional advertising, marketing and promotional functionality and services, including distribution of print or digital catalogs or promotional communications.
  * Provide you with ACCO promotional emails, and manage your preferences regarding such communications. 
  * Identify your preferences to customize our communications and marketing and provide you with a personalized experience.
  * Post content provided by you, such as product reviews, on the Digital Services.
  * Invite you to participate in Promotions or surveys.
  * Administer and fulfill Promotions, including tax reporting.
  * Improve our products, services, merchandise selection, Digital Services, marketing and promotional efforts and customer service.
  * Develop and manage internal administrative and analytical processes and records.
  * Enable us to track and measure the effectiveness of digital advertising and marketing services.
  * Any other purpose you have authorized.

### **6\. How We Share Your Information with Others**

#### _Non-Personal Information:_

Unless otherwise prohibited by law, ACCO Brands may share your non-personal information with third parties for any purpose, including third-party marketing efforts. This non-personal information may include aggregate data, which is compiled data reflecting the collective usage of multiple users. We may also share de-identified information. De-identified information is not personally identifiable, but it does reflect the usage patterns of a particular use of the Digital Services, as opposed to users collectively.

#### _Personal Information:_

_With Your Authorization:_

ACCO Brands may transfer your information to third parties if you authorize such disclosure.

_Without Your Authorization:_

We may share your personal information in the following circumstances or with the following entities without your authorization as follows:

_The ACCO Brands Family_

We may share or transfer your personal information to our subsidiaries and corporate affiliates, including future subsidiaries and affiliates. These companies may use your information for their own marketing purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

_Third-Party Service Providers_

ACCO Brands may share or transfer your personal information with third-party service providers. These third parties may include providers of services including hosting, maintenance and support services, payment processing and authorization, order processing, shipping, fraud protection and risk reduction, email distribution, mail delivery, marketing and advertising, market research and Promotions management and fulfillment, among others.

_Third-Party Marketing and Sales_

We may make your personal information, together with information regarding your shopping activity, demographics, and product preferences, available to third parties for ACCO’s, the third-party’s, or others’ marketing purposes.

We may also offer certain carefully chosen third-party products or services through the Digital Services. Should you choose to accept an offer from a third party, we may provide that third party with your personal information in order to facilitate the service or transaction that you request.

_Business Reorganization or Sale_

In the event that ACCO Brands merges with or becomes part of another organization, or in the event that we are sold, sell all or substantially all of our assets, sell a line of business or are otherwise reorganized, your personal information may be one of the assets transferred to the acquiring or reorganized entity.

_As Required by Law or to Protect Rights_

ACCO Brands reserves the right to release your information (i) to comply with any law, rule or regulation, when we are under legal compulsion to do so (such as a subpoena or court order), or when we otherwise believe that the law requires us to do so, (ii) to investigate and help prevent security threats, fraud or other malicious activity, (iii) when ACCO Brands believes it is necessary to protect or enforce the rights, property interests, or safety of ACCO Brands, our employees, the users of our Digital Services or others, or (iv) as ACCO Brands deems necessary to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and otherwise enforce the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.

_Social Media and Advertising Platforms_

We may use platforms such as Facebook® to offer you advertising based on your interests. In order to offer these ads, we may disclose personal information, such as email addresses, social media ID or handle, or phone numbers, to the platform provider, which can match this information to a particular platform user.

_Information Collected by Third Parties_

In some instances, we may allow third parties to use online tools to collect information about you when you use the Digital Services. For more information, please see the Cookies and Other Technologies and Targeted Advertising sections of this Privacy Policy.

### **7\. Cookies and Other Technologies**

ACCO Brands uses technologies, including, without limitation, cookies and pixel tags, in connection with the Digital Services.

_Cookies_

Cookies are small data files transmitted by a website and stored on your computer or device. The Digital Services use both session cookies, which do not stay on your computer after you close your browser, and persistent cookies, which remain on your computer until you delete them or they expire. Our use of cookies includes, but may not be limited to:

  * To permit our Digital Services to function properly and enhance user experience, such as remembering the items in your shopping cart, storing your preferences, recognizing you when you return to the Digital Services, providing a personalized experience, and helping you login to your account.
  * To implement analytics tools, including Google Analytics, that help us understand how the Digital Services are performing and how visitors engage with the Digital Services.
  * To improve and track our advertising, including to connect your activity across multiple visits and multiple ACCO Brands websites, to monitor your interaction with our advertising campaigns, to customize content and marketing on the Digital Services, and for Targeted Advertising.
  * To identify other information about you, including your name, email address, and mailing address, and to send you digital and print marketing materials.

_Pixel Tags_

ACCO Brands uses pixel tags, which are tiny graphic images (also known as web beacons, action tags, or transparent GIF files). Our use of pixel tags includes, but may not be limited to:

  * To tell us which parts of the Digital Services you have visited and to measure the effectiveness of any searches you may perform on the Digital Services.
  * To send you email messages in a format you can read and let us know when you have opened a message from us and whether you click on the links contained in the message.
  * We or our ad marketing partners may use pixel tags to track your interaction with online advertising, measure the performance of a marketing effort, and for Targeted Advertising.

_Embedded Links_

Links provided in our emails and, in some cases, on third-party websites may include tracking embedded in the link. The tracking is accomplished through a redirection system. The redirection system allows ACCO Brands to understand how the link is being used. Some of these links will enable ACCO brands to determine that you have clicked on the link. This information may be combined with the personal information that we have about you. We use this information to evaluate and improve our services and the performance of our marketing campaigns.

_Managing Cookies_

Most browsers accept cookies by default, but you can usually block or restrict cookies on your computer or device or purge them from your browser by adjusting your browser preferences. You should consult the user guide for your browser or mobile device for instructions on how to configure settings to meet your preferences. Cookies allow you to take advantage of some features of the Digital Services, so if you block or restrict cookies, you may not be able to use some features of the Digital Services. To learn more about Google Analytics and your privacy choices in connection with Google Analytics, including the Google Analytics Browser Opt-Out Add On, please visit the Google website at [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/ "Google Analytics Browser Opt-Out")/.

For more information regarding your privacy choices in connection with cookies and other technologies, see the Targeted Advertising section of this Privacy Policy.

### **8\. Targeted Advertising**

ACCO Brands’ advertisements are shown on third-party websites and platforms and our Digital Services may display advertising from third parties. We and our vendors, including Google, use technologies cookies and pixel tags to help manage online advertising and to serve ads to you based on your online activity, including past visits to the Digital Services and visits to third-party websites and platforms. These technologies may be provided by us or our vendors and may allow us or the vendors to recognize a unique cookie or pixel tag placed by us or by third parties when you access the Digital Services or when you visit third-party websites or platforms. They also allow us and our vendors to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites and platforms so we or they can manage advertising effectiveness and provide you with online advertisements, including without limitation advertisements on third-party websites and platforms, more likely to be of interest to you. These technologies also allow us to learn which advertisements bring users to our Digital Services.

For more information about targeted advertising and your choice to opt-out of receiving targeted online advertisements, visit the following:

  * To opt-out from targeted advertising from members of the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA), please visit the DAA website. <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>
  * To opt-out of targeted advertising from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI), please visit the NAI website. <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>

Please note that these opt-out mechanisms are browser specific. If you wish to opt-out of targeted advertising across all browsers, you need to visit the above websites from each browser you use. Also, please be aware that if you opt out of receiving targeted advertising, you will still be served with advertisements, but they will no longer be targeted to your interests.

### **9\. Your Privacy Choices**

_Promotional Email Communications from ACCO Brands_

ACCO Brands wants to provide you with relevant information regarding our products and services. You can choose which promotional email communications to receive from us by logging in to “My Account” and adjusting your communication preferences. In addition, you can manage your email preferences by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in any promotional email we send you and following the procedures indicated. Please note that even if you opt out of receiving promotional emails from us, we will send you transaction emails and respond to questions from you.

_Print Catalogs_

If you no longer wish to receive print catalogs from us, please contact us with a request to be removed from our print catalog mailing list and provide your exact name and address, or the mailing label from your catalog, so that we can identify you correctly. Because mailings are planned in advance, it may take several weeks for your request to become effective. If you continue to receive unwanted print catalogs, please contact us again.

_Do Not Track (“DNT”) Signals_

Although your browser may deliver a DNT signal to the Digital Services, ACCO Brands does not currently respond to DNT signals.

_Cookies and Other Technologies; Targeted Advertising_

For information on how you can control cookies, please review the Cookies and Other Technologies section of this Privacy Policy. For information on how to exercise choices regarding targeted advertising, see the Targeted Advertising section of this Privacy Policy.

### **10\. Security**

Although ACCO Brands uses Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") security technology to safeguard your shopping transactions and encrypt your payment information, no website, server or application is completely secure. We cannot promise that your personal information will not be disclosed or misused, either by accident or by the unauthorized acts of others, such as “hackers.” We urge you to be careful online. This includes not sharing your user names and passwords

The Digital Services may contain customer reviews, message boards and other areas allowing you to post content on the Digital Services or share it with your social media accounts. Please remember that any information disclosed in this manner becomes public information. You agree that ACCO Brands is not responsible for material posted by you or others in these public forums.

### **11\. Links to Other Sites**

_Other ACCO Brands Websites and Digital Platforms_

This Privacy Policy applies only to the ACCO Brands Digital Services on which it is posted. Other ACCO Brands websites (including those for intended for different countries), social media sites, and applications may have different privacy policies. Please read the privacy policy posted on each ACCO Brands website, social media site, application or other digital platform that you visit to understand the information collection, use and sharing practices that apply.

_Third-Party Websites and Digital Platforms_

The Digital Services may link to websites and digital platforms operated by third parties. These websites operate independently of ACCO Brands and have their own privacy policies and terms of use which differ from those of ACCO Brands. We encourage you to review the privacy policy and terms of use posted on each third-party website you visit.

### **12\. Updating Your Information**

Some ACCO Brands Digital Services allow or require users to set up an account. If you have an account, you can access and update your account information by logging in to the “My Account” section. You may also update certain customer information (name, address, telephone number and email address) by contacting us. Please note that you may not be able to access or update all information we have about you.

### **13\. Children**

The Digital Services are intended for use by adults only. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us personal information, you can contact us to remove such information

In addition, California minors (under 18 years of age) may in certain circumstances request and obtain removal of content or information they posted to the Digital Services. If you are a California minor, you may make a removal request by contacting us.

### **14\. Consent to Data Transfer**

ACCO Brands is a global organization, with legal entities, business processes, management structures, and technical systems across the world. By providing your personal information to us, you are indicating your express consent to have your information transferred, processed, and stored globally, including in countries outside the United States, whose privacy and data protection laws may be less comprehensive than those in the United States.

### **15\. Notice to California Residents - Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California’s "Shine the Light" law, California residents who provide personal information when obtaining products or services for personal, family, or household use are entitled to request and obtain from ACCO Brands certain information about the personal information we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. To obtain this information, please contact us, with "Request for California Privacy Information" in the subject line of your correspondence or email. Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the "Shine the Light" requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.

### **16\. Notice to Individuals Located Outside of the United States**

This site is intended only for individuals located in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please visit one of our sites for your region. Specifically, if you reside in a member state of the European Economic Area (the European Union as well as Lichtenstein, Norway, and Iceland), please visit one of our E.U.-based websites.

### **17\. Contact Us**

We always welcome your questions and feedback. For privacy-related issues, please contact us at:

Consumer Affairs  
PO Box 540  
Booneville, MS 38829

Toll-free: 800.648.6323  
Fax: 800.941.4461  
Email: [DataPrivacy@acco.com](mailto:DataPrivacy@acco.com "E-mail DataPrivacy@acco.com")
